♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
♪ Family Guy 11x06 ♪ Lois Comes Out of Her Shell
Lois的第二春
翻译&注释:wudixny 校对&压制:zurica @familyguy贴吧字幕组
好了 我要去商店了
All right, I'm going to the store.
还有人要带什么吗
Anybody need anything?
嗯 你能帮我买副国际象棋和反戴的帽子么
Yeah, can you get me a chess set and a backwards hat?
我得给明天去给旧城区的
I got some inner-city school kids
孩子们启发点拨一下
I gotta inspire tomorrow.
好的 Darius 指向国王
Okay, Darius, point to the king.
没错 就是你
That's right. It's you.
嘿 Lois 是不是呃 某人
Hey, Lois. Doesn't, uh, somebody have
这周就过生日了么
a birthday coming up this week?
噢 你能记得真好 Brian
Oh, it's nice of you to remember, Brian,
但说实话 我倒宁愿这生日悄悄过去
but, frankly, I'd rather let this one slip by.
我不需要被提醒自己有多老
I don't need to be reminded how old I'm gettin'.
知道么 这很可笑
You know, it's funny.
你一直忙于照顾孩子
You keep so busy with your kids,
而时间似乎也悄悄飞逝
time just seems to slip away,
等你某天转过身来却发现…
and then you turn around one day and...
好了 再见 别制造噪音了
Okay, bye. Stop making noise.
其实 Peter 我知道Lois虽然说不重视
You know, Peter, I know Lois is downplaying it,
但我想她一定会很感激的
but I think she might actually appreciate it
如果我们给她办个生日派对
if we threw her a party.
也许是个惊喜派对更好
Maybe even a surprise party.
好主意 Brian
That's a great idea, Brian!
是啊 我爱派对
Yeah, I love parties.
我是说 我在迎婴派对上玩得很开心
I mean, I had a great time at my baby shower.
嗯 在打开所有的礼物以后
Well, after opening all these gifts,
我也许可以给我自己来点酒了
I could use a little wine right now myself.
咕嘟 咕嘟 咕嘟 咕嘟
Glug, glug, glug, glug.
你能想象吗
Can you imagine?!
我很抱歉 我的荷尔蒙现在真是让我疯狂
I'm sorry. My hormones are just crazy right now!
Stewie 你想来次妈咪火箭旅行么
Stewie, you want a Mommy rocket ride?
什么 你什么意思
What? What do you mean?
出发咯 准备好发射吧
Here we go! Get ready for blastoff!
嗷 狗日的
Ow! Son of a bitch!
上帝 Stewie 你还好吧
Oh, my God, Stewie, are you all right?
扔的漂亮 凯西安东尼
Nice throw, Casey Anthony.
曾被指控谋杀亲生女儿 后被判罪名不成立
天 我希望在希尔斯肖像工作室
Oh, my God, I hope the guys at Sears portrait studio
北美的一家全数字化照相连锁店
能够把这张脸润色好
will be able to retouch this.
我说什么呢
What am I saying?
他们肯定会的 他们可是希尔斯啊
Of course they will. They're Sears.
什么玩意儿
What the deuce?
你好呀
Well, hello there.
我说你可真是个小萌物啊
I say, you're a cute little fellow.
告诉我: 你觉得罗斯麦高恩怎么样
Tell me something: What do you think about Rose McGowan?
美国演员 歌手 代表作有《圣女魔咒》《刑房》等
没错 她也让我的便便缩回去了
Yeah, she makes my turtlehead go in, too.
"turtlehead"是指拉出一半的屎
那米歇尔罗德里格兹怎么样
How about Michelle Rodriguez?
美国演员 代表作《速度与激情》系列
恩 我也这么感觉的 有一点 对吧
Yeah, me too, kinda, right?
你懂的 她有种假小子的特质
You know, she's got like a cute tomboy thing
让你觉得你能和她一起玩垒球
where you feel like you could play softball with her,
但是之后给她整条"香肠"
and then later on, give her the old sau-seege.
我喜欢你
I like you.
我感觉得出我们将会成为好朋友
I can tell we're going to be good friends.
我们有那种秃子之间的默契
We've got that unspoken bond that all bald guys have.
我还以为他绝不会离开呢
I thought he'd never leave.
我也是
Me neither.
爽
Yeah.
啊 你们刚才干那件事了么
Aw, did you guys just do the thing?
好了 我们一会见 再见 好了 各位
Okay, we'll see you soon. Bye. All right, you guys,
刚才是Lois 她10分钟后到
that was Lois. She's gonna be here in ten minutes.
爸 你是怎么把妈骗出去好让我们装饰的
Dad, how did you get Mom out of the house so we could decorate?
这个 Chris 我建了
Well, Chris, I constructed
一个精雕细琢的假超市
a very elaborate fake grocery store.
天啊
Oh, my God!
这些腌黄瓜真的只要3毛9么
Are these pickles really only 39 cents?!
没错 女士
That's right, ma'am.
哇 太棒了
Wow! This is incredible!
这到底是怎么回事
What the hell's going on here?
这里是我的玩具
And over here are my toys.
这是我的消防车 玩具弹簧 弹性橡皮泥
This is my fire truck, my Slinky, my Silly Putty.
你懂的 弹性橡皮泥(可笑泥)很赞的
You know, Silly Putty's awesome,
但你知道什么才是真酷么 严肃泥
but you know what's really cool? Serious Putty.
噢 这个看上去好好玩
Oh, this looks like fun!
上面说我得了癌症
It says I have cancer.
我们觉得这样可能更好些
We thought it would be better
让你从蛋中的化学物质上得知这个消息
if you heard it from chemicals in an egg.
嘿 Stewie 你最好下来
Hey, Stewie, you better come down.
派对快开始了
The party's about to start.
那是什么 是只乌龟么
What is that? Is that a turtle?
没错 Brian 我在公园找到的
Yes, Brian. I found him at the park.
我叫他Sheldon
I named him Sheldon.
噢 告诉你: 我是今天带他回来的
Oh, and get this: I brought him home today,
巧的是今天正好是
and coincidentally this is the day
Rupert重新开始锻炼的日子
Rupert started working out again.
真是显而易见
So transparent.
Rupert 你的眼睛怎么了
Rupert? What happened to your eye?
Brian 是你把Rupert的一只眼睛拽掉了么
Brian, did you pull one of Rupert's eyes off?
不 我怎么会干这种事呢
No. Why would I do that?
也许是你乌龟干的
Maybe your turtle did it.
胡说 Sheldon可是有颗温柔的心
Nonsense. Sheldon is a gentle soul.
他不会伤害任何人
He wouldn't hurt anybody.
好吧 快走 我们下楼
Well, come on. Let's get downstairs.
Lois马上就回来了
Lois will be here any minute.
惊喜
Surprise!
呀 生日
Yay! Birthday!
天啊
Oh, my God!
生日快乐 Lois
Happy birthday, Lois!
你们不用这样的
You guys shouldn't have done this!
嘿 你随时可以庆祝自己绝经了
Hey, anytime you can celebrate the end of someone's periods.
各位 各位 我有话要说
Everyone, everyone, I have something to say.
给我最亲爱的Lois
To my dearest Lois on her birthday.
我们一起经历了一场前所未有的旅程
What a journey we've had together.
你知道 生活不停地改变着一切
You know, life has a way of changing things.
两座曾经坚固雄伟的"山峰"
What were once two firm, impressive mountain peaks
变成了荒芜的 采掘过的 泥泞"土坡"
have become a barren, strip-mined, muddy landslide
都下垂到底了
that droops ever downward.
曾经粉色多汁的玫瑰"花瓣"
What were once pink and succulent rose petals
各位看官自行脑补
现在成了破烂不堪
now take the form of the shredded, raggedy,
恶作剧雪茄爆炸后的末端
blown-out endpiece of a practical joker's exploding cigar.
Peter 够-够了
Peter, that- that's enough.
Lois 你也许不再是
Lois, you may not be
我当初见到的小母马
the young filly you were when I met you,
但你仍是我可信赖的老耕马
but you're still my reliable old plow horse
每一天
who's there each day
都会拉拉犁 在谷仓帮忙
to pull the plow, to help around the barn,
然后让丈夫马偶尔抽抽她
and let the husband horse-slap a batch at her now and then.
好了 我想就这些了
Well, I guess that's it.
我爱你 甜心
I love you, sweetheart.
而我有一份掌嘴的礼物
And I have a lovely gift of the batchslapping variety
正等着你 先等我喝下适量的酒之后
waiting for you when I'm just the right amount of drunk.
敬Lois
To Lois!
- Lois - 妈
- Lois! - Mom!
天 她什么鬼毛病啊
Geez, what the hell's her problem?
Peter 她已经对年龄感到不安了
Peter, she was already feeling insecure about her age,
而你还对她说了那么一番刻薄的话
and then you went and gave her that horrible speech!
我不怪她
I don't blame her.
没人喜欢在大庭广众之下被羞辱
Nobody likes to be humiliated in public.
我是国王Stewie
I'm King Stewie!
我用铁腕来统治王国
I rule with an iron fist!
啦 啦啦 啦啦 啦啦 看我 喔
La, la-la, la-la la-la! Look at me! Ooh!
到我办公室去 马上
In my office. Now.
嘿 你们有谁看见你们妈了么
Hey, any of you guys seen your mother?
她昨晚一直没上床
She never came to bed last night,
我到处都找不到她
and I can't find her anywhere.
搞什么鬼
What the hell?
嘿 骚货们
Hey, sluts!
天 别瞪着我 好么谢谢
OMG, stop staring at me, please-'kay-thanks.
妈 你还好么
Mom, are you okay?
Lois 怎么回事
Lois, what's goin' on?
就这么回事 Peter
I'm what's goin' on, Peter.
我去做了挑染 逛了商场
I got highlights, I went shopping,
还给我那里做了…
and I had my...
所以现在更紧了
So it's tighter now.
Peter 我想Lois可能正在经历中年危机
Peter, I think Lois might be having a midlife crisis.
来吧 伙计们 谁想坐我的车兜风
Come on, dudes! Who wants to hop in my wheels
然后去海边玩极限飞盘的
and head to the beach for some ultimate Frisbee?
没错 Sheldon 我和你一样
Yeah, Sheldon, I'm with you.
我不…我不会这招
I can't... I can't do that.
嘿 推特控们
Hey, tweeps!
开玩笑啦 我没关注你们 你们弱爆了
JK, I don't follow you, you're lame.
看看谁刚弄了个超屌的新纹身
But look who just got herself a sick new tat.
天啊 妈
Oh, my God, Mom!
"serenity" 宁静
我知道 我也不敢相信
I know, I can't believe it either.
我觉得我的缺点之一就是有点勇敢啦
I guess one of my flaws is I'm just kinda brave.
不 那个其实很给力 因为现在
No, that's great actually, because now
不管谁走在你背后 都知道你有60块钱了
anyone walking behind you will know that you had $60.
喔 屌爆了 Lois
Wow! That is awesome, Lois!
你的臀部就像NBA球员的胳膊一样
Your bum looks like an NBA guy's arm.
不过这不是付钱请人来安装
'Cept it's not payin' someone to install
一部PS游戏机在车里
a PlayStation in a car.
Lois 你知道纹身是永久性的么
Lois, you do know that's permanent?
好啊 那就是说
Good. Then that means
我的屁股会看起来永远年轻了
my ass is gonna look young forever.
各位 我 呃 我要对着水槽来一发
Guys, I, uh, I gotta go shoot one into the sink.
怎么回事
What's going on?
妈妈的行为和穿着就像20岁
Mom's acting and dressing like a 20-year-old.
我知道 很担心她
I know, and I'm worried about her.
你不能冒充自己不能胜任的角色
You can't just pretend to be something you're not.
是啊 问问剪刀手爱德华就懂了
Yes, just ask Edward Scissorhands.
约翰尼德普主演的同名电影 由其本人配音
没错 我是个优秀的夜间保姆 你们俩去
Okay, now, I'm an excellent night nurse, so you two get
好好睡上一觉 不用担心任何事
some much-deserved sleep and don't worry about a thing.
我会好好爱护这个美妙的小宝贝的
I will take such loving care of this wonderful little gift.
等你们休息好 醒来后
And when you wake up, well-rested,
你们金贵的小宝宝会微笑得
your precious little baby will be smiling
像阳光一样灿烂
as bright as the sun.
他死了
It's dead.
可我提醒你 我还不会阅读
And while I remind you I can't read yet,
我只能想象麦德兰会这么说
I can only imagine Madeline would say,
系列同名儿童读物的主角 生活在法国巴黎
"带我离开这恶心的法国医院
"Take me out of this disgusting French hospital
帮我找到真正的父母吧"
and find me some real parents."
啊 纸割伤我了
Ah! Paper cut!
一个刀片
A razor blade?!
谁他妈会把刀片当书签啊
Who the hell uses a razor blade as a bookmark?!
好吧 非常搞笑 Stewie
All right, very funny, Stewie.
- 什么 - 什么什么意思
- What? - What do you mean, what?
你把我的杰克丹尼威士忌换成了无味的健怡可乐
You replaced my Jack Daniels with flat Diet Coke.
我没有
No, I didn't.
你有看到现在才早上8点20么
And you're noticing this at 8:20 in the morning?
你的生活怎么了
What has happened to your life?
你想谈谈么
Do you need to talk?
离我的酒远点
Just stay away from my booze!
不是我 Brian
It wasn't me, Brian.
好 如果不是你 那是谁
Well, if it wasn't you, who was it?
我是说 最近有许多怪事
I mean, there's a lot of weird stuff
在这里发生
going on around here lately.
就在昨天 有人给Peter来了个"热屁股"恶作剧
Just yesterday, somebody gave Peter a "hotbutt."
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦 正常的生活 ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la, regular life ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦... ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, l... ♪
然后有人把Meg的安眠药
And then somebody replaced Meg's sleeping pills
换成了消食泡腾片
with Alka-Seltzer.
人们会想念我 当我…
People are gonna miss me when I'm...
好吧 我肯定这些事一定有个非常
Well, I'm sure there's a perfectly logical explanation
合乎逻辑的解释
for those things.
有时你只需…
Sometimes you just...
哇 好险
Whoa, that was close.
是啊 那东西怎么会倒的
Yeah, how'd that thing fall over?
好吧 谁把我的眼镜换成叉子了
Okay, who replaced my glasses with forks?
我是说 他们用来看叉子是很清楚
I mean, they're real good for seeing forks
但就没有别的用了啊
but not much else.
Peter 你能到下面的洗衣房来么
Peter, can you come down to the laundry room?
呃 烦死人了
Ugh, son of a bitch.
如果她再把我的皮带洗了
If she washed my belt again,
我要用我干裂 枯萎的皮带抽她
I am gonna hit her with my dry, withered belt.
什么事 Lois
What is it, Lois?
我正在看…
I was watching...
喔 Lois 你在干什么呀
Whoa, Lois, what the hell are you doing?
干我 Peter 就在这地下室(臀部)干我
Do me, Peter, do me right here in the basement.
你是说我们呆的地方还是你的屁股
Y-You mean this room we're in or your bum?
不 这间房里 Peter 就在地毯(阴毛)上
No, this room, Peter, right here on the carpet.
噢 原来你是说从前面
Oh, so you mean the front.
赶紧过来亲我
Just get over here and kiss me.
让我们在这干净 叠好的衣物上做爱吧
Let's have sex on all the clean, folded laundry.
哇 Lois 我得说 我喜欢全新的你
Wow, Lois, I got to say, I like this new you.
我喜欢极了
I like it a lot.
噢 Peter
Oh, Peter!
- 噢 Peter 爽 - 吔
- Oh, Peter, yes! - Yeah.
- 噢 我欲火焚身了 - 吔
- Oh, I'm on fire. - Yeah.
- 拿下我 你这下流的杂种 - 吔 噢
- Take me, you filthy bastard. - Yeah, oh.
- 毁灭我还有这衣物吧 - 哦吔
- Destroy me and this laundry. - Oh, yeah.
吔 这里 把Meg的胸罩放你嘴里
Yeah, here, put Meg's bra in your mouth.
上帝 这令人太不安了
Oh, my God, that's so disturbing.
我知道 恶心死了
I know, gross.
是啊 而且我的听力比你们好多了
Yeah, and my hearing's a lot better,
所以我还听见了 抽吸之类的声音
so I hear, like, suction and stuff.
♪ "我死前的愿望就是能找点乐子" ♪
♪ "All I wanna do is have a little fun before I die" ♪
All I Wanna Do - Sheryl Crow
♪ 我身边不知从何处冒出的男子如是说 ♪
♪ Says the man next to me out of nowhere ♪
[烂人帽店]
♪ 世界上的好人们 ♪
♪ The good people of the world ♪
♪ 正在午餐的空档中洗他们的车 ♪
♪ Are washing their cars on their lunch break ♪
♪ 尽力冲水擦洗 ♪
♪ Hosing and scrubbing as best they can ♪
♪ 穿着短裙和西服 ♪
♪ In skirts and suits ♪
♪ 他们开着闪亮的达特桑和别克车 ♪
♪ They drive their shiny Datsuns and Buicks ♪
♪ 驶回电话公司还有唱片店 ♪
♪ Back to the phone company, the record store, too ♪
♪ 但他们完全与比利和我不同 ♪
♪ Well, they're nothing like Billy and me ♪
♪ 因为我只想要找些乐子 ♪
♪ 'Cause all I wanna do is have some fun ♪
♪ 我感觉我并不是唯一 ♪
♪ I got a feeling I'm not the only one ♪
♪ 我只想要找些乐子 ♪
♪ All I wanna do is have some fun ♪
[贱货法则]
♪ 我感觉我并不是唯一 ♪
♪ I got a feeling I'm not the only one ♪
抱歉造成这些破坏 我老婆正在经历她的更年期
♪ 我唯一想要的只是找些乐子 ♪
♪ All I want to do is have some fun ♪
♪ 直到太阳晒到圣塔莫尼卡大道 ♪
♪ Until the sun comes up over Santa Monica Boulevard. ♪
位于美国加州
Sheldon 你干嘛呢
Sheldon. What are you doing?
回你自己的缸里去
Get back in your bowl where you belong.
既然我醒了 还不如就朝Lois嘴里吐口水吧
Well, long as I'm up, I might as well go spit in Lois's mouth.
Sheldon?
振作 Stewie
Come on, Stewie.
他只是只小乌龟
He's just a little turtle.
他伤害不了你的
He can't hurt you.
出去
Get out!
这是不是嗨爆了 Peter
Isn't this epic, Peter?
那DJ真是有两下子
That DJ has got some mad skills.
你说他们在吧台会卖安乃近(镇痛药)么
You think they sell Anacin at the bar?
来嘛
Come on.
起来和我跳舞 Peter
Get up and dance with me, Peter.
这地方真疯狂
This place is sick.
太对了
Hells yeah!
这是普罗维登斯唯一的天台泳池
It is the only rooftop pool in Providence.
罗德岛州首府
无意冒犯 但这地方太棒了
No offense, but this place is awesome.
我-我-- 我哪里被这句话
I-I-- Where was I supposed to be offended
冒犯到了
within that remark?
我们 我们可以走了么 Lois
Can we, can we leave, Lois?
其实 我们正要走
Actually, we are leaving.
我们要去镇里另一边的疯狂派对
We're hitting another insane party across town.
什么 你是说现在
What, you mean now?
Peter 你听着就像个老古董
Peter, you sound like an old fart.
我以为你喜欢有个年轻火辣的老婆呢
I thought you liked having a hot, young wife.
我之前确实如此 但是新鲜感已经没了
Well, I did at first, but the novelty's worn off.
就像我9/11开始写的那个博客一样
Same thing happened with that blog I started on 9/11.
2001.9.11
美利坚永不死 我们永远不会忘记
2005.5.04
刚看了《怪兽婆婆》 还不赖 我想战争还在继续
詹尼弗洛佩兹2005年主演的电影
2011.8.18
有人知道如何把喷漆从婴儿眼中弄出去吗
听着 Peter 你想干什么随便你
Look, Peter, you do what you want to do,
但我要去那个派对
but I'm going to that party.
我的生活还没有完结 才刚刚开始
My life isn't over. It's just beginning.
所以如果你不愿随着野马奔驰
So if you don't want to run with the wild horses,
那就回马厩里睡觉吧
then go back to the barn and go to bed.
但是 Lois…
But, Lois...
傻逼地方还没有把我的东西干洗好
Stupid place still doesn't have my dry cleaning.
这里可不是干洗店 这是一家跳舞俱乐部
That's not a dry cleaners. It's a dance club.
是吗
It is?
那这倒是解释了不少事
Well, that explains a lot.
噢 这歌完全是我的菜
Oh, this is my jam!
天 Peter 你看上去糟透了
Jeez, Peter, you look terrible.
我知道 Lois让我筋疲力尽
I know. Lois has been wearing me out.
我已经跟不上她了
I just can't keep up with her.
我不知道她想证明什么 Brian
I don't know what she's trying to prove, Brian,
但我再也受不了了
but I can't take it anymore.
Peter 你还不明白么
Peter, can't you see?
她这么做是因为你
She's doing this because of you.
天啊 是你叫她耕马的
For God's sake, you called her a plow horse.
不奇怪她想证明自己还年轻有活力
It's no wonder she's trying to prove she's young and vibrant.
晚上好 我是Tom Tucker
Good evening, I'm Tom Tucker.
圆蛤市今晚遭受
The city of Quahog has been stricken
了一场比伯热潮
with a case of Bieber Fever tonight,
作为少年偶像和假冒黑人的贾斯汀比伯
as teen idol and fake black guy Justin Bieber
正在圆蛤市文娱中心举行表演 座无虚席
is in town for a sold-out show at the Quahog Civic Center.
我们现在连线到现场的
We now go live
亚洲记者Tricia Takanawa了解更多内容
to Asian correspondent Tricia Takanawa with more.
Tom 我正站在
Tom, I'm standing here
圆蛤市文娱中心前
at the Quahog Civic Center,
周围充斥着满满的前青春期爱液
awash in a pool of prepubescent sexual moisture.
哦吼 我们爱你 贾斯汀
Woo-hoo! We love you, Justin!
- 看啊 - 那是老妈
- Look! - That's Mom!
- 上帝 - 搞毛呢
- Oh, my God! - What the hell?
她居然在贾斯汀比伯演唱会
She's at a Justin Bieber concert?
呃 贾斯汀比伯完全是过去式了
Ugh, Justin Bieber's so yesterday.
现在Quentin Vashay才是我的全部
I'm all about Quentin Vashay now.
Quentin Vashay是谁
Who's Quentin Vashay?
完全正确
Exactly.
怎么回事
What's going on?
我们现在要找个新妈了么
Do we have to get a new mom now?
不 Chris
No, Chris.
我要去把咱们以前的妈妈找回来
I'm gonna go get our old mom back.
如果是我让她产生这种想法的话
If I'm the one who made her feel this way,
那么解铃还需系铃人
then I'm the one who's got to fix it.
Brian 钥匙
Brian, keys!
Chris 啤酒
Chris, beer!
Meg 丑逼
Meg, ugly!
嗯哼 是的
Mm-hmm. Yes.
是 我知道了
Yes, I see.
Rupert 报社的人
Rupert, the man from the newspaper
想援引一句你对我舞蹈能力的评论
would like a quote from you about my dancing abilities.
Rupert?
你去哪儿了
Where'd you go?
木兰纸杯蛋糕
Magnolia Cupcakes?
Rupert 上帝啊
Rupert! Oh, my God!
噢 天 不要
Oh, my God, no!
如果是他对你做了这些 我发誓要杀了他
If he did this to you, I swear I'll kill him!
那这个布卢明代尔百货公司的盒子怎么又在这里
And what's that box from Bloomingdale's doing here?
我 呃 我-我不认识这人
I, uh, I-I don't know who this is.
天啊 他真可爱
Oh, my God, he is so adorable.
我就应该咬他 吃掉他
I could just bite him and eat him up.
我知道 他太完美了
I know, he's perfect.
他就像个男女孩合体
He's like a boy and a girl.
是啊
I know!
抱歉 你不允许进去
Sorry, you're not allowed in here.
噢 是么
Oh, yeah?
我对这个不感兴趣
I'm not into that.
哦
Oh.
那你对什么有兴趣
Well, what are you into?
粉红浆果
Pinkberry.
美国的冰酸奶连锁店
我爱我的工作
I love my job.
好吃 好吃 好吃 好吃 好吃 好吃 好吃 好吃
Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum.
你好啊 帅小伙儿
Hey, there, cutie.
哦 嘿 你好啊
Oh, hey. How's it going?
呃 你是我妈的朋友么
Um, are you a friend of my mom's?
没错 我是你妈的朋友 鲁宾逊太太
Yeah. I'm your mom's friend, Mrs. Robinson.
电影《毕业生》中勾引男学生的荡妇
我不…我不明白
I don't... I don't get that.
那是什么引用么
Is that a reference to something?
呃 那好吧
Uh, okay.
那 我 呃-- 对了 我是硬条他妈
Uh, I'm, uh-- oh, I'm Stifler's mom.
《美国派》系列电影中上了硬条同学的荡妇
还是不知道
Still no idea.
好吧 你只要脱掉裤子就好 甜心
Okay, just get your pants off, hon.
给我住手 离她远点
Stop right there! Get away from her!
- Peter - 你是谁
- Peter?!- Who are you?
你是怎么进来的
How'd you get in here?
离开我老婆 你这个装着橡子鸡鸡的美人
Step away from my wife, you acorn-penised beauty!
听着 我发誓 什么都没发生
Look, I swear. Nothing happened.
放松 老家伙
Just relax, old man.
老家伙
Old man?!
怎么 你觉得你不会变老么 小混蛋
What, you think you're not gonna get old, you little bastard?!
还有 Lois 我也受够你了
And, Lois, I've had enough of you, too!
现在 你给我回家 表现出你这年纪该有的样子
Now, you come home and start acting your age!
不要 Peter 我不想那样
No, Peter. I don't want to act my age,
你也不想
and you don't want that either.
否则你就不会喊我老耕马了
Otherwise, you wouldn't have called me an old plow horse.
听着 我不是有意那么说的
Look, I didn't mean to say that.
我-我是个混蛋
I-I was a jerk.
但这不就是你想要的么
But isn't this what you want?
你难道不想我保持青春活力么
Don't you want me to stay young and exciting?
我以为我想
Well, I thought I did.
我是说 每个人结婚了一段时间后
I mean, every guy who's been married a while
都以为他想要一个年轻火辣的妞
thinks he wants a hot, young chick,
但是和她们待上一小时后
but after you spend an hour with one of them,
你就想把自己给爆头了
you want to blow your brains out.
但是 Peter 我这么做只是为了让你开心
But, Peter, I was just doing this to make you happy.
你确实让我开心了 Lois
You do make me happy, Lois.
你是我生命中最美好的事物
You're the best thing that's ever happened to me.
你真好
That's sweet.
但你得承认 我和以前不一样了
But you got to admit, I'm not what I used to be.
我也是
Well, neither am I.
我以前是个驯狮员
I used to be a lion tamer.
听着 Lois 我会永远珍惜
Look, Lois, I'll always treasure
那个我年轻时遇到的野性小辣妹
the wild, little hottie I met when I was young.
但我不想在和一个孩子在一起了
But I don't want to be with a kid anymore.
我想要的是个聪明性感美丽的中年伴侣
I want a smart, sexy, beautiful, middle-aged companion.
我想要的是真实的Lois
I want the real Lois.
我的Lois
My Lois.
噢 Peter
Oh, Peter.
Bieber先生 他们要求您再表演一首
Mr. Bieber, they're calling for an encore!
天啊 那些孩子正期待一场表演呢
Oh, my God, those kids are expecting a show.
我会处理的
I'll handle this.
女士们先生们 Conway Bieber先生
Ladies and gentlemen, Mr. Conway Bieber.
恶搞美著名乡村歌手Conway Twitty
♪ 人们在各地看见我们 ♪
♪ People see us everywhere ♪
♪ 他们以为你真的会在乎 ♪
♪ They think you really care ♪
It's Only Make Believe - Conway Twitty
♪ 但我不能欺骗自己 ♪
♪ But myself I can't deceive ♪
♪ 我知道这都是想象… ♪
♪ I know it's only make-believe... ♪
呵呵 看看谁露出真面目了
STEWIE: Well, well, look who has surfaced.
你感觉越来越冷了
You're getting colder.
嘿 滚出来和我对打
Hey, get out here and fight me!
妈的
Damn it!
现在击球的是: Stewie Griffin
Now batting: Stewie Griffin!
噢 我日
Oh, crap.
呃 你看起来就像裸体的拉里戴维
Ugh, you look like a nude Larry David.
《宋飞传》和《周六夜现场》编剧 秃顶
不 不 不要
No, no, no!
天啊 超级马里奥
Oh, my God, Super Mario?
你在这儿干嘛呢
What are you doing here?
我跳上了一只乌龟 Stewie
I jump on a turtle, Stewie.
虽然这生活不怎么让人激动 但这就是我的生活
It's not an exciting life, but it's my life.
你能回来真好 妈
It sure is good to have you back, Mom.
是啊 我们很想你
Yeah, we missed you.
谢谢你们能容忍我
Well, thanks for putting up with me, you guys.
很抱歉我因为年龄问题而失控
Sorry I got so flipped out about my age.
啊 别担心 Lois
Aw, don't worry about it, Lois.
但从现在起 你要记住
But from now on, remember:
无论怎么样我都爱你
I love you just the way you are.
而且 35岁也没什么错嘛
And besides, there's nothing wrong with being 35.
Peter 我43了
Peter, I'm 43.
滚出这房子
Get out of this house.
翻译&注释:wudixny 校对&压制:zurica @familyguy贴吧字幕组